buzzsharer.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - BuzzSharer.com

**Privacy Policy for Buzzsharer.com**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at buzzsharer.com@gmail.com.

At Buzzsharer.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by Buzzsharer.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other web sites, Buzzsharer.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Buzzsharer.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies, web beacons, and similar technologies to collect or receive information from our website and elsewhere on the Internet and use that information to provide measurement services and target ads. Buzzsharer.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

**Links to other Websites**

Buzzsharer.com may contain links to enable you to visit other websites of interest easily. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
